Wife to the king. Icon to the world. Destined for more.
Priscilla is a drama, romance film directed by Sofia Coppola.
When teenage Priscilla Beaulieu meets Elvis Presley at a party, the man who is already a meteoric rock-and-roll superstar becomes
someone entirely unexpected in private moments: a thrilling crush, an ally in loneliness, a vulnerable best friend.
Priscilla, played by Cailee Spaeny.
Elvis, played by Jacob Elordi.
Captain Beaulieu, played by Ari Cohen.
Ann Beaulieu, played by Dagmara Dominczyk.
Vernon Presley, played by Tim Post.
Grandma 'Dodger', played by Lynne Griffin.
Priscilla is a 2023 American biographical drama film written, directed, and produced by Sofia Coppola, based on the
1985 memoir Elvis and Me by Priscilla Presley (who serves as an executive producer) and Sandra Harmon.
It follows the life of Priscilla (Cailee Spaeny) and her complicated
romantic relationship with Elvis Presley (Jacob Elordi).
Priscilla premiered at the 80th Venice International Film Festival on
September 4, 2023, where Spaeny won the Volpi Cup for Best Actress.
It was released in the United States by A24 in select theaters on
October 27, 2023, before expanding wide on November 3, 2023.
It received generally positive reviews from critics
and grossed $33 million worldwide.
In addition to her award from Venice, Spaeny received a Best Actress
nomination at the Golden Globe Awards for her performance.
The film explores themes of jealousy, husband wife
relationship, obsession, 1970s, drug addiction.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.